Hello, and welcome to the Predictive Analytics for Business Nanodegree program.
您好 欢迎使用 Predictive Analytics for Business Nanodegrey 程序
I'm Sam, and I'll be your host for the program,
我是萨姆我是你的节目主持人
which means I'll pop up here and there to provide more context to what you're learning.
这意味着我会在这里和那里弹出来为您正在学习的内容提供更多背景信息。
Now, the overarching goal of the program is to advance your career by
现在 该计划的总体目标是通过以下方法推进您的事业 :
helping you develop predictive analytic skills that are applicable to business.
帮助您开发适用于业务的预测分析技能
In order to accomplish this goal,
为了实现这个目标
there are set of skills that you need to acquire.
有一套你需要的技能
You'll learn to structure problems, clean,
你会学会结构问题清洁
format and transform data,
格式和变换数据
and use a variety of analytical techniques to solve business problems.
并使用多种分析技术来解决业务问题
You'll use Alteryx to analyze A/B test,
你会用 Alteryx 来分析 A/B 测试
create forecast, and build machine learning models.
创建预测 并构建机器学习模型
If you're interested in going into
如果你有兴趣去
more detail about what you'll learn during the program,
更详细的介绍你在节目中所学习的内容
spend a moment reading the syllabus,
花点时间阅读教学大纲
and before getting started,
在开始之前
go through the orientation.
穿过方向
It will provide more details on the various resources you'll have access to.
它将提供有关您可以访问的各种资源的更多详细信息
Tell you how project submissions work,
告诉您项目提交的工作方式
and provide a few study tips that are most successful students use.
并提供一些最成功的学生使用的学习技巧 。
最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6